ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: LABOR UNITY
  - K-Mart Import Protest 7/85., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 114 Includes: signing Textile Bill petition, Springfield, Ill. K-Mart; Midwest Conference, Cammie Howard and Gilbert Watson; Knoxville K-Mart; Gary Ferraris at Knoxville, Tenn. Shopping mall.
  - Knight, Tom. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 115 Includes: meeting.
  - Knitting/Carpet Conference, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 116 Includes: meeting; contact sheet.
  - Knitting Division. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 117 Includes: founding of ACTWU Knitting Division; contact sheets.
  - Knoxville Press Conference., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 118 Includes: London Fog workers Halloween Festival, Knoxville; Sen Sasser; Knoxville 11/84 Sr Jt Bd; meeting; contact sheet, Knoxville Allied-Chem Press Conference.
  - Kuhns, Ellie. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 119 Includes: Wilkes Barre, Pa. union plant visit, Kuhns campaign for Mondale.
  - Labor Bookshelf. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 120 Includes: Chicago Central States Joint Board; books; contact sheet.
  - Labor Council for Latin America. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 121 Includes: Washington conference: Luis Madura, Santos Crespo (Local 92), Bruce Dunton.
  - Labor Day Mass (St. Patrick's)., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 122 Includes: 1976 marchers; Cardinal Cooke greets Charles and Elizabeth Garrahan, NY.
  - Labor Endorsed Candidates (East)., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 123 Includes: Howell Heflin; Bruce Morrison; William Ratchford; Joseph Biden; Barbara Kennelly; Gerald Johnson; Libby Mitchell; Barry Hobbins; Norman D'Amours; Clarence Long; Bill Bradley; James Howard; James Hu
  - Labor Endorsed Candidates (West)., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 124 Includes: John Kerry; Nancy Dick; David Pryor; Bill Alexander; Beryl Anthony; Paul Simon; Marty Russo; Lane Evans; Dan Rostenkowski; Wayne Townsend; Tom Harkin; Walter Huddleston; Joan Growe; William F. Wint
  - Labor in the 80s. (Box 25, Folder 21)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 125 Includes: workers (male, female, Black, White).
  - Labor Law Demo Wash. DC, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 126 Includes: contact sheets; march for Dinkins.
  - Labor Law Reform., 1977 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 127 Includes: cartoons, clergymen speak at House hearings; unions testify; Hearings Roanoke Rapids, NC 8/9/77; S. Carolina attorney John Bolt Culhertson; Ohio Congressman John Ashbrook; John Dunlop; Darlington w
  - Labor Leaders., 1977 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 128 Includes: groups shots- misc. Jewish Labor Committee 2/77.
  - Labor Leaders Advisory Council (Ret.). (Box 25, Folder 25)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 129 Includes: Morton Goldklang, Irving Aronberg, Murray Goldstein, Jack Rubenstein; Sol Stetin, Gene Kluger, Herbert Levine.
  - Labor Research Associates Dinner. (Box 25, Folder 26)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 130 Includes: contact sheets.
  - Labor Roundup., 1988 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 131 Includes: IP strike 1988; Job Corps training camp PAI 9/88; 11/88 meatpackers' tools; 1988 OCAW "Break the Lockout" march; UFW VP Dolores Huerta.
  - LaCapria, Vincent., 1974 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 132 Includes: Receiving award 10/25/74.
  - LaFollette, Sr. (Senator). (Box 25, Folder 29)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 133 Includes: close-up.
  - LaFollette, TN (LU 11/12/90)., 1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 134 Includes: contact sheet, TN teachers.
  - LaGreca, Carmine. (Box 25, Folder 31)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 135 Includes: portrait.
  - LaGuardia, Mayor FH., 1937 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 136 Includes: Lawrence, Mass. Speech, 1937; Bowling Tournament 3/1937; portrait.
  - Laminates Unlimited Baltimore. (Box 25, Folder 33)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 137 Includes: group shot.
  - Landman, Jerry. (Box 25, Folder 34)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 138 Includes: two men.
  - Lanzilli, Basillo. (Box 25, Folder 35)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 139 Includes: Sam Beshwaty, Buzzy Lanzelli, Nick Magliano, Al Ferullo, Sam Tacredo, Joe Frascone.
  - LaRocque, Admiral (Ret.) Dir. Center for Defense Information. (Box 25, Folder 36)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 140 Includes: S.W. Regional Joint Boarding meeting- speech.
  - Las Vegas/Frontier Demo Dec. 1992. (Box 25, Folder 37)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 141 Includes: march.
  - Latin-American Women Trade Unionists Delegation (Anchor Dye & Finishing). (Box 25, Folder 38)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 142 Includes: fringe machine; contact sheets.
  - Lautman, Harry. (Box 25, Folder 39)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 143 Includes: group shots; Lautman and Henoch Mendelsund; at convention; Lawrence Day Participants, Mass.
  - Leadership Conference (Columbus, GA) 79. (Box 25, Folder 40)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 144 Includes: leadership school; graduates; Eagle & Phoenix workers.
  - League for Industrial Democracy. (Box 25, Folder 41)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 145 Includes: meeting.
  - Leahy, Patrick (D-Vt.). (Box 25, Folder 42)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 146 Includes: Leahy, Pilusc, Palmer; close-up; portrait.
  - Leather & Apparel Testimony. (Box 25, Folder 43)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 147 Includes: contact sheets; Local 178, Jacob Sheinkman, Arthur Gundersheim.
  - Lee, Robert., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 148 Includes: 1976 Convention speeches.
  - Lehigh Valley Joint Board., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 149 Includes: Irene Pruznick; Retirees group marches, Washington, 7/30/84, Sheinkman and Salee; Jennie Vandever and Sue Hahn; Angie Grandinetti and Ann Reuss.
  - Levi Employees (U.S.). (Box 25, Folder 46)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 150 Includes: preparing Levi samples; contract signing at Levi-Strauss; Local 503 Charleston, SC group shot.
  - Levin, Carl. (Box 25, Folder 47)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 151 Includes: portraits.
  - Levy, Leonard., 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 152 Includes: speeches; Levy presents charter to Local 1414-C at Xerox plant, 5/11/76, S. Calif. JB meeting; Southern Calif. Jt. Bd. Retirees party 12/77; Levy Testimonial, Los Angeles: Levy blows out birthday c
  - Lewis, David (NDP Federal Leader)., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 153 Includes: David Lewis addresses participants attending Testimonial Dinner in his Honour, 1976.
  - Lewis, John L., 1937 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 154 Includes: speech; group shots; 5/37 negatives; Jennings, Joseph Salerno, Anthony Valente, August Bellanca, Sidney Hillman, John L. Lewis, Hyman Blumberg; Washington, DC Lewis testifies before House labor com
  - Lewis, Richard., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 155 Includes: portrait; 1976 interview shots; speech.
  - Lewis, Richard Lee. (Box 25, Folder 52)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 156 Includes: J.P. Stevens (Black) worker's arm healing, Montgomery, Ala.
  - Libbey Co.- Lewiston, Maine(Local 385. (Box 25, Folder 53)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 157 Includes: negotiating team group shot.
  - Liberal Party., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 158 Includes: 1976 contact sheet.
  - Library Story. (Box 25, Folder 55)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 159 Includes: Pulaski County (Indiana) Library receiving Local 785 Labor Bookshelf; Plymouth Public Library, Rochester, Indiana, receiving Local 785 Labor Bookshelf; man reading. Includes: Pulaski County (Indi
  - License Plate. (Box 25, Folder 56)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly - b5, ff 160 Includes: "Last in wages" NC license plate.
  - Lieberman, Harry. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Includes: 100 year old clothing cutter.
  - Lincoln, Abraham. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Includes: cartoon; hand-drawn portrait; actor alongside image of Lincoln.
  - Lincoln Brass. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Includes: workers celebrating union victory Jacksboro, TN.
  - Lincoln Memorial. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Includes: Howard Anthony, W. Williams, M.G. Burnside, Marie Spurlock at Memorial with wreaths.
  - Linds, Saul. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Includes: Man at display; man at desk, JP Stevens campaign, Montreal Jt. Board.
  - Lithograph (by Reuvin Rubin). (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Includes: Man making sword.
  - Livery Drivers. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Includes: contact sheet; negatives.
  - Lofts Story (New York). (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Includes: contact sheets; people in shop; Dell Clothing workers, Dominic Cappello and Murray Cohen; 692 Broadway, Manhatten.
  - Love, Harriet. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Includes: Local 169 (Black) woman studies at Rutgers University library, Newark, N.J.
  - L& P Distributors, Southbridge Mass. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Includes: L&P in-plant team, paper workers (Hispanic).
  - Lumber., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Includes: off-bearing rough lumber as it comes from the mill in the woods near New Philadelphia, Ohio, June 1949.
  - MacFadyen, Richard., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Includes: speech, MacFadyen and Alton Hodgeman; portrait; 1980 contact sheet; close-up; 1980 group shot.
  - Made-In-USA. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Includes: label.
  - Madison, Wisconsin (Newspaper Strike). (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Includes: Big "Scab Entrance" sign at newspaper plant.
  - Mailing Computerization. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Includes: (Indian) woman operating computer terminal, Amalgamated Life Insurance Company.
  - Mailing (Labor Unity). (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Includes: Contact sheet; (Black) workers in shop, St. Johns.
  - Makoski, Chet., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Includes: 1985 portrait, Cleveland; 1984 portrait; various portraits; group shot.
  - Malloy, Sara. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Includes: Malloy receiving New York Consumer Assembly's award: Malloy, Edward Katz, Louis Levine, Finley; Black Trade Unionists honor Malloy: Cecil Topin, Malloy, John Burnell, Frederick O'Neal.
  - Mancini, Joe. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Includes: Men in store; Mancini in store; contact sheets.
  - Mandel, Marvin(former governor of Md). (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Includes: Group shot.
  - Manes, Max., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Includes: 8/89 portrait.
  - Mabton Cork, Cranford NJ., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Includes: 10/6/88 newly organized shop, contact sheet; group shots.
  - Manzardo, Eve. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Includes: Chicago, Manzardo retires as head of Samuel Levin Retirement Center, with Finley.
  - Margolius, Sidney. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Includes: Contact sheet.
  - Marshall, Ray (U.S. Secretary of Labor)., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Includes: Addresses NLRB dinner 3/2/77, Washington, DC; Marshall discusses the Energy Crisis with George Meany, Lane Kirkland, Sheinkman; being sworn in, Jimmy Carter; GEB meeting mid-October, Washington, DC; Sol Stetin shakes hands with Marshall.
  - Marshall, Thurgood. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Includes: Portrait.
  - Martin Guitar Strike. (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Includes: Striking guitar maker, picket line at Martin Guitar.
  - Martinez, Jose (Dr.)., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Includes: Man at desk, Baltimore, 1977; contact sheet.
  - Marvin, David. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Includes: School Board Election winner standing outside Maplewood High School, Local 81, Meadville, Pa.
  - Maska, U.S. Inc. Bradford, VT. (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Includes: Union negotiating committee.
  - Masland Carpet Contract. (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Includes: Negotiating table: Robert Hinkle, Carl Frazier, Dick Plescia, Local 1739 officers; tallying picketing assignments at strike headquarters; Local 1739 strikers.
  - Massachusetts. (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Includes: Watertown, Mass. group shot; Worcester, Mass. worker meeting; contact sheet.
  - Master, Bob. (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Includes: Contact sheet, Bob Master cake.
  - Matewan - film. (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Includes: Organizing miners.
  - Mathias, Charles (R-MD). (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Includes: Speaking shots.
  - Mathis, Jake., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Includes: Retirement ceremony, December 1977, Sol Stetin, William DuChessi, Scott Hoyman, Paul Swaity, Billy Buck.
  - Mattey, Andrew. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Mayekisu, Moses. Empty. (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Mazariego, Jose-El Salvador Anstel., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Includes: 7/89; 6/89; meeting, June 1989; Mazariego and Jack Sheinkman in El Salvador, June 1989.
  - McBride, Lloyd, Pres. of United Steel Workers. of America. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Includes: Installation: Sol Stetin, McBride, Allan Kistler.
  - McCulley, Nellie., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Includes: ACWA member recalls Rice-Stix strike, of 1952.
  - McGovern, George (D-SD). (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Includes: Portraits; with his wife; Washington, Aug. 20 addresses platform Democratic Committee; Labor for McGovern-Shriver; touring industrial plants in New England.
  - McGregor Strike-Canada (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Includes: Toronto Local 1058C; McGregor Strike, Canada, strikers.
  - McIver, Harold. (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Includes: Harold McIver, Harry Golden; McIver, Roanoke Rapids, NC, Congressional Hearings; contact sheet; Harold McIver, Bruce Raynor; McIver and Linda Ray enter Stevens Dunean plant.
  - McKee, Don. (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Includes: Husband and wife; contact sheets; negatives.
  - McKnight, James. (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Includes: Portrait; retirement dinner: McKnight, Joseph Coponi, William DuChessi.
  - McLaughlin, Ann. (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Meany, George., 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Includes: Meany at Convention podium July 1976, DuChessi, Sheinkman, Stetin, Finley; George Meany 12/77; Washington Press Conference, Sheinkman, Meany, DuChessi, Arthur Goldberg; Finley and Meany confer during AFL-CIO convention; Local 7587 makes tie for
  - Meany, George Labor Studies Center Silver Springs, MD. (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Includes: B.A. Course at Meany Center, group shot; ACTWU staff at Meany Labor Center; ACTWU organizers meet at Meany Center; ACTWU staff members at Meany School; new (Black) graduate of Meany Center; graduates with their new diplomas.
  - Medical Examinations. (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Includes: Employees filling out forms for past medical history; blood being drawn from employee for tests; doctor checking employee x-ray.
  - Meir, Golda. (Box 6, Folder 51)
    Includes: Meir talking; Finley and Stetin meeting with Meir.
  - Melcher, John. (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Includes: Melcher for Senator.
  - Merola, Mike., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Includes: Contact sheet; speaking, 1974; Convention shot, 1981; reading Convention Proceedings 1981; in buffet line at retirement dinner 9/26/81.
  - Merrill, Phillip (Democratic Congressional Candidate)Maine., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    Includes: Merrill in Brunswick, Me. 1982.
  - Metzenbaum, Howard., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Includes: Greeting ACTWU Legislative Conference Delegates, 1976; group shot; with Henry Seibert; campaign propaganda.
  - Metzenbaum, Howard Sen (D-Ohio). (Box 6, Folder 56)
    Includes: Portraits.
  - Metzger, Bishop Sidney., 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    Includes: Speaking at convention, 1981; touring shop floor 1980; Sidney Metzger receives plaque from El Paso Jt. Bd. 1978.
  - Mexican 19th Sept. Garment Workers. (Box 6, Folder 58)
    Includes: Mexican women from the Mexican 19th of September Union visit the ACTWU Headwear Joint Board.
  - M. Fine. (Box 6, Folder 59)
    Includes: M. Fine workers; KY Lt. Gov. Paul Patton and Allan Fine; Ribbon cutting, Lt. Gov. Paul Patton, Allan Fine.
  - Michigan State AFL-CIO., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    Includes: Justice G. Mennen "Soapy" Williams of the Michigan Supreme Court, Murray Finley, and David Chaney, 1976; Michigan State AFL-CIO Sept. 12-16, 1976.
  - Mid-Atlantic Reg. Conf. Nov. 1987 and 1988., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    Includes: Lloyd H. Davis; 11/19/88 contact sheets; Henry Morton, Local 2331; Local 1739 Masland Carpet negotiating committee; meeting Jack Sheinkman at 11/88 award ceremony; Allentown, PA Conference 11/17/87; 11/7/87 group shot; Virginia Keyser, 11/18/88
  - Mid-Atlantic Reg. Jt. Bd.., 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    Includes: Crawford Mfg. negotiating committee (Black women) Richmond, Va.; Julia Beadle, winner of Wayne Dernoncourt Scholarship Award, with Bruce (cont'd) Dunton, Betty Zello, Warwick Daniel, William Cannon, Janet Beadle, Marlene Williams; officer instal
  - Midtown Bank (First Contract) Chicago. (Box 6, Folder 63)
    Includes: Employees.
  - Midwest Leadership School (Springfield). (Box 6, Folder 64)
    Includes: Billy Reason over (black) Local 1437; Roy Findley, Pres. Local 1490 and Donna Shelley, Local 335; contact sheets.
  - Midwest Regional Conf., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    Includes: Contact sheets; 10/2/87 writing letters to senators against Bork nomination; 10/87 workshop on Civil Rights led by Clayola Brown.
  - Midwest Regional Conference (textile Division). (Box 6, Folder 66)
    Includes: Indianapolis James Walraven discusses problems with Johnson and Johnson coordinating Council; Local 1758 woman; Sheinkman addresses conference: Charles Sallee, Noel Beasley, Clayola Brown, Ray Mullins; writing letters to Congress against Bork no
  - Midwest Regional Joint Board., 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    Includes: JP Stevens Boycott Staff at Milwaukee strategy meeting: James Cleary, Murray Finley, Del Mileski, Ron Hooks, Barbara Merrill; Sol Brandzel, Bert De Mers, Bill Crutcher, John Perkins; contact sheets; Rep. Aspin addresses delegates, Milwaukee; Mil
  - Midwest Reg. Jt. Board/Conf. Empty., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Midwest Regional Leadership Conference (Textile), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    Includes: Local 1893 woman speaks; Local 1805 woman thinking; Springfield May 1977 Conference; contact sheets; Local 941 (Black) woman; Local 194 woman; Sol Stetin speaks; Local 375 (Black) man listening; men conferring.
  - Migratory Workers., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    Includes: Home of a migrant worker, 3/1/59.
  - Mikulski, Barbara (D-MD). (Box 26, Folder 1)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 71 Includes: Delivers rousing message at Baltimore Hdq.; speaks to COPE Institute delegates; waving at podium.
  - Mikva, Abner(Illinois). (Box 26, Folder 2)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 72 Includes: Mikva addresses delegates at the ACTWU COPE/Legislative Conference, Washington.
  - Mileski, Del. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 73 Includes: at GEB meeting; appointed Union Label Dept. Director; various shots.
  - Milledgeville (spy Plot) Story. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 74 Includes: Robert Rice, manager Milledgeville, GA; Charles Osborne, Chief of Police, Milledgeville, GA; JP Stevens workers; man on street, at city hall, etc.
  - Miller, Joyce., 1976-1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 75 Includes: "AFL-CIO Women Working for '84" committee; Washington Press Conference: Lillian Moss, Miller, Elmer Chatak, William Boardman; James Joy Jr. presents award to Miller, NYC Labor Council; receiving the
  - Miller, Joyce., 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 76 Includes: Accepting WDL Clendenin Award Finley, Jacob Clayman, William Ross, Adrienne Critchlow; addresses AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, 12/77; 1981 speech; 1979 Illinois State Convention speech; UAW one-
  - Miller, Ruth. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 77 Includes: at dinner; with two men.
  - Miller, Vera., 1977-1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 78 Includes: Insurance Committee at 1981 Convention; speaking 1977; speaking 1985.
  - Millinery Contract Local 24-42H., 1986 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 79 Includes: Voting, Grossman and Sons, Passaic, NJ; Millinery Contract, 1986; group shot.
  - Minimum Wage., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 80 Includes: "Labor News Conference" radio show: Andrew Biemiller, Frank Swoboda, Dale McFeatters 1977; Congressmen contact sheets; Coalition for a Fair Minimum Wage, first meeting; youth cashier at McDonalds's
  - Mink, Patsy. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 81 Includes: (Asian) woman at convention.
  - Minnesota Joint Board. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 82 Includes: M. Liman Mfg, Onamia, Min.; retirement party; elections; banquet; speech.
  - Miscellaneous-June, 1980. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 83 Includes: NBU; contact sheet (Black) female union members.
  - Miscellaneous- Unidentified- Dec 1980. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 84 Includes: janitors; John Handcox receives the 1st Joe Hill Award, Great Labor Arts Exchange, George Meany Center, Silver Spring, Md.: Joe Glazer, Handcox, Pete Seeger; female retirees, cake.
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 84B Includes: "mysterious mixture."
  - Mission Employe(sic)., 1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 85 Includes: Mision Empleo (sic) 4/87; Contact sheet: NYC Shoe workers Meeting, JTPA "Mission Employment"; Contact sheet: NY Retirees Council and Missions Empleo (sic).
  - Mississippi Joint Board., 1979-1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 86 Includes: Officer installation 1979: Thomas Knight, James Jackson, Virginia McWilliams, Margaret Driskell, Sue Wright. Edna Carter, Floye Berry, Dimple Herring, John Morrow; installation, Hattiesburg 1982: Flo
  - Moffett, Toby. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 87 Includes: Sitting with other representatives; contact sheet.
  - Molori, Ralph. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 88 Includes: March, "Don't Buy Imports."
  - Monas, David J. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 89 Includes: portrait.
  - Mondale, Joan., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 90 Includes: 1976 sews a union label on a suit at Eagle Clothes in Brooklyn, Finley, Sheinkman; workers of Eagle Clothes welcome Ms. Mondale; contact sheets 1976 campaign, visiting Eagle Clothes.
  - Mondale Rally 3/24/84 Sheraton Centre., 1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 91 Includes: contact sheets.
  - Mondale, Walter., 1973-1980 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    --Collection re-housed - formerly, b6, ff 92 Includes: gives "thumbs up" at Philadelphia victory rally; Joan Mondale, 1976; addresses overflow crowd of trade unionists at ACTWU hall, Los Angeles; union members speak out for Mondale, Ferraro; portraits; g